Contact

rebeccajgreenberg@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/rjgrn (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing

Healthcare

Patient Education

Languages

Spanish (Professional Working)

Certifications

Certified Emergency Nurse (CEN) Trauma Nurse Core Certification Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS)

Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS)

Family Nurse Practitioner (FNP)

Honors-Awards

Dean's List

Dean's List

Zeta Pi Chapter, Member

UTHealth Faculty Award of Excellence

HANP Scholarship Recipient

Rebecca Greenberg, MSN, APRN, FNP-C

Registered Nurse at AMN Healthcare

Houston, Texas

Summary

Licensed and certified new-graduate Advanced Practice Nurse
Practitioner, graduated Summa Cum Laude from UTHealth School of
Nursing in the Texas Medical Center with over 7 years' experience
in emergency nursing at high-acuity teaching hospitals, seeking to
obtain employment as Family Nurse Practitioner in outpatient clinic,
providing holistic high-quality evidence-based care to all populations
with emphasis on patient education and health promotion.

Experience

Harris Health System Suppplemental RN- LBJ Emergency Center April 2020 - Present (4 months)

Houston, Texas, United States

AMN Healthcare

Registered Nurse Emergency Department September 2019 - April 2020 (8 months)

Lyndon B. Johnson Hospital, Emergency Department, Houston, TX

The Methodist Hospital System
Registered Nurse Emergency Department
February 2013 - May 2019 (6 years 4 months)
Houston, Texas

Ascended RN Pathway to Leadership from new grad to RN III

High acuity emergency department nursing at level III designated teaching hospital

Worked in all areas, including triage, fast-track, emergency and observation Preceptor to students and new hires

Active house wide committee member (Magnet Committee, Professional Nurse Advisory Board)

Active member of shared governance committee

Education

The University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston (UTHealth)

Masters of Science, Family Practice Nurse/Nursing · (2018 - 2019)

The University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston BSN, Nursing · (2011 - 2012)

Emory University

Bachelor of Arts (B.A.), Anthropology · (2007 - 2011)